Lesson seven is cost management.
And so these are the learning objectives
for cost management.
First of all, you want
to understand exactly
what is cost, the principles
of cost management.
So we'll talk about the different types of
cost and how that impacts your project.
You need to appreciate the value of
managing costs.
So you don't want to be going over budget.
And of course, we want to learn all the
common tools, the common tools and the
common tools and artifacts used for cost
management and then one of the major
sections then is going to be learning
about earned value right earned value
management and you know there's a whole
section on formulas right so you really
need to understand and learn these earned
value management formulas